kulukfunds.com 2010-05-04

# Kuluk Funds

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  |   
| 

Kuluk Funds respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security.

We know that you are concerned with how your personal and financial information is treated. This Privacy Policy sets forth our current policies and demonstrates our commitment to your financial privacy. Please bear in mind, however, that we may change the content or services found on our Web site, and consequently, our privacy policy at any time in the future. Please revisit this page from time to time to be sure that you are familiar with any changes to our policy. Your continued use of our web site following any modifications to this privacy policy will be conclusively deemed acceptance of any changes. Kuluk Funds is committed to safeguarding the personal information you provide us. This privacy policy describes how we handle and protect personal information we collect about individuals who apply for or receive our products and services. The provisions of this notice apply to former customers as well as our current customers.

We not share information about our clients with any third parties for their independent use in marketing their products. We do not disclose nor do we reserve the right to disclose, any nonpublic personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone, except to other nonaffiliated third parties as required by law.

**Protection Of Your Personal Information**

We maintain personal information in a password-protected electronic file outside of our Web site or its servers, and we limit access to such information to employees who need to have such information to provide services to you. We will only use such information about you to verify your identity and eligibility to receive certain products or services, to provide information to you about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you, to record your interest in products and services that we offer, and to respond to your requests for information.

Our employees are required to maintain and protect the confidentiality of your personal information and must follow established procedures to do so. We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. We do not rent or sell your name or personal information to anyone.

By joined with Kuluk Funds, you declare that you have read, understood, and accepted our Privacy Policy.

|   
|  |
